grizzlyape.com 2011-05-19

# Privacy Policy

## GRIZZLYAPE.COM

**  
Dated October 2010**

This policy (the "Privacy Policy") tells you how GrizzlyApe.com collects information from you, how we protect it and how we use it.

**  
What type of information we collect about you**

We will collect your email address when you obtain materials from us, such as themes, add-ons, screen savers, and software.

**  
What we do with personally identifiable information**

This information may be used for marketing and for market research purposes, including internal demographic studies, to provide, optimise and personalise our services, and to send you newsletters and information, which we collectively refer to as "marketing communications."

**  
You may opt-out from receiving such marketing communications from us.**

We may use a variety of technical methods such as cookies and web beacons to collate information (see the section below on "Use of Cookies" for further information).

You may unsubscribe from email communications via unsubscribe links provided in communications sent to you.

**  
Who else has access to the information we collect?**

We will only pass on your information to third parties in the following situations

  * if this was clearly stated at the time of collection or registration and, where required, if you have given permission for this;
  * If we sell the GrizzlyApe.com to another organisation or merge with another business. In such a happenstance, the buyer will only be able to use your information as set out in this Privacy Policy;
  * If we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary for legal proceedings. We may also disclose information when we believe in good faith that applicable law or regulation requires it or to protect the safety or security of users of our Site; and
  * If we use third party processors to administer and process your personal information for the purposes notified in the Privacy Policy, e.g. for hosting activities related to the use of our Sites or services. We may also share details with third parties (such as auditors or legal advisors) to obtain advice. Any such processing will be governed by an agreement in the form required by law, preserving any statutory data protection rights.

**Policies for children**

Our terms of service states that minors may not use our website. We do not knowingly collect information from minors.

**Use of cookies and web beacons**

We collect information through technology to make our Site and other content or services which we make available to you more interesting and useful to you. For instance, when you come to our Site via your computer or other media device, we may place cookies and web beacons on our Site which may be used to collect information about the sections you visit, the products you are interested in and the frequency with which you visit various parts of our Site. You agree that we collect your IP address or other unique identifier. At times, we also use these identifiers to collect information regarding the frequency with which our visitors visit various parts of our Site. We may combine your IP address with other personally identifiable information for marketing and for market research purposes, including internal demographic studies, so we can optimize our products and services and customize the Site for you.

Our Site uses a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including cookies and web beacons.

Cookies are pieces of information that a Site sends to your computer or other media device while you are viewing or interacting with the Site. We use cookies for a variety of purposes including tracking usage on our Site in order to- enhance our visitors' experience on our Site and to learn more about your preferences and interests. For instance, when you return to one of our Site after logging in via your computer, cookies provide information to the Site so that the Site will remember who you are ("visitor session information"). You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies.

You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. We may use cookies to analyse the traffic patterns on our Site, such as the frequency which our users visit various parts of our Site.

Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of Site. We also use these technical methods to analyse the traffic patterns on our Site, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our Site.

We may combine your visitor session information or other information collected through cookies, web beacons and other technical methods with personally identifiable information in order to understand and improve your online experiences and to determine what products, promotions and services you prefer or are likely to be of interest to you.  
We also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we send our visitors for a number of purposes including: to determine whether our users have opened or forwarded those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e-mails; to customise the display of the banner advertisements and other messages after a visitor has closed an email; and to determine whether a visitor has made an enquiry or purchase in response to a particular email.

Cookies, web beacons and other technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorised by us to collect information on our behalf. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that identifies you personally.

You may get cookies from our advertisers. We do not control these cookies, and once you have clicked on the advertisement and left our Site our Privacy Policy no longer applies.

**  
Links to other sites**

You should be aware that when you are on our Site you could be directed to other sites where the personal information collected is outside of our control.

For example, if you click on a banner advertisement the result may take you to a third party site. The privacy policy of the new site will govern the information obtained from you on that site.

**  
Changes to this policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and we will post the latest version on this on Site. If we ever wish to use your personal information in a way which is incompatible with the information in this Privacy Policy, we will only do so with your consent.

**Queries**

If you have queries about our use of your personal information or wish to have your personal information removed, you can [contact us here](http://www.grizzlyape.com/contact-us/).

View our [Terms of Use](http://www.grizzlyape.com/terms-of-use/) here.
